I guess I should have kept
looking in the city after all.
No, in the city there's a high likelihood
they'd be picked up by kids,
and above all, they're easy to find there.
Ooh, a nice wide-open space.
It should be easy to search here.
Hey.
What are you doing?
--Uh, I'm just a--
--Liar.
You're a gatherer too, aren't you?
Well, this is my turf.
I'll give you a choice.
Die now... Or help me find the coins.
I'll pass on both!
What should I do?
What's the right move here? I don't know!
There's no information to go on!
"Three hours earlier"
"Keep Out"
"Suspicious persons will be
reported to the police immediately"
Well, do you smell any humans?
No. I don't think there's anyone around here.
No surprise, huh?
There aren't any trails
this deep in the mountains--
I don't think we'll find any people
out picking wildflowers!
In other words, if we run into anyone out here,
it's safe to assume they're a monster.
What'll you do if we actually run into one?
Honestly, it depends on what they do.
Ideally, we'd see them
before they see us and attack--
We can't do that!
We won't know if they're good or evil!
I thought you'd say that!
Although we won't last long
if we fight every person we meet.
Plus, what we really need now is information.
The alien told us we could
find lots of coins here,
but in a big area like this,
we're not going to find anything
just looking around randomly.
We need to know exactly
where the other coins were found
and how many other monsters
or "gatherers" there are here.
Who are the strongest ones?
Where are they and what are they doing?
We don't know anything.
If we find someone,
you should transform right away.
We'll probably find them before they find us...
Since you have that powerful nose.
Are you sure I should transform?
What if they're just a normal person?
Dumbass. Remember?
Only monsters will come up here.
It's the opposite of the town.
Up here, we need to hide our real faces.
If we encounter someone bad
and they see who we are,
our normal lives will be in danger.
They could threaten
to tell our school or our family,
or worse yet, our friends and family
could get caught up in the fight.
Of course, facing them in
your monster form will put them on guard.
Isn't it fascinating, though?
Huh?
Two monsters that don't know
each other's background, personality,
or abilities, clashing with each other
in the middle of the mountains?
I wonder what'll happen.
Clair, wait!
Don't go that way!
Someone is there.
Are they nearby?
I don't know.
But it seems like they're not that close...
Maybe 200 meters off.
Good. I have time to take off my clothes.
Hurry up and transform.
No way! Clair!
We'll make the first move.
We could avoid danger
and steadily gather up coins.
That might seem like the
right approach at first glance.
But it's not.
While you're taking your time,
someone else could gather
all the coins and gain their power.
If you're afraid of taking a risk,
you'll be too slow.
In this world...
The right approach is to meet the risk head on.
It's big.
Way bigger than me.
And what's with those hands?
If it attacks me with those...
This is the first time
an enemy has approached me.
Enemy?
I've felt the presence of
gatherers many times before,
but as soon as they see me, they run.
I'm not your enemy. I just want to talk to you.
Your voice... You're a girl.
I see. Too bad.
Well, I guess I shouldn't expect too much.
Are you alone, too?
How clever! She's making him
think there's only one person here.
You want to talk about the coins, right?
Sorry, but I don't know much about them.
Same here. I was hoping we could help each--
I did not come her to look for coins.
I wanted strength,
and this is what I got from the alien.
But when I used it on normal people,
they were nothing.
I couldn't get a feel for
my new strength at all.
I want to know how strong I am.
The alien told me I could meet
other "gatherers" here.
Honestly, I'm not excited about fighting a girl,
but I can't move forward without sacrifice.
I'm sorry, but we must fight.
I might have made a mistake here.
Shuichi, you idiot.
Excellent.
A normal human would have
been killed instantly by that strike.
But I withstood it.
That answers one question.
He's so strong...
No... We'll be crushed...
Shuichi. That's enough.
I'll take care of this.
Clair!
That was a solid strike! I could feel it!
We're in trouble.
This guy might be out of our league.
I used the first monster we fought as
a standard to predict others' strength.
But if everyone out here is like this guy...
Like her...
Clair...
We can't die now...
Isn't that enough? I think we know now--
You're much stronger than me.
But I didn't come here to fight you.
The coins, huh? What do
you want them for, anyway?
Nothing, really.
But if that kind of power ends up
in the hands of someone dangerous,
there's no telling what they'll use it for.
That's why I want to share
as much information as possible--
I see.
Well then, how can you prove
that you are not someone dangerous?
Everyone searching for the coins,
everyone that seeks power thinks that way.
They think everyone else is an enemy.
That's how this place works.
That's why I came here.
Too bad.
I thought we could be friends.
You good, Shuichi?
Yeah. I'm ready for this.
I knew there would be fights
we couldn't avoid here...
And when they come, I won't hesitate!
That answers another question.
My body can withstand bullets.
Although it did pierce one of my arms...
That isn't a normal gun, is it?
I was able to predict, to some degree,
where you'd aim, which allowed me to react.
Even if I was slightly off.
I was confident that you would aim to kill.
Allow me to thank you.
My name is Tadanori Sanbe.
I'm a sophomore at Yamakita University.
You're revealing your identity?
This is my way of saying thank you.
You fought with your life, to take mine.
You deserve thanks.
Now it's my turn.
I always desired strength
and learned various martial arts.
But those methods were
created by humans, for humans.
They don't quite fit this form.
What the hell is that stance?
I came up with my own martial art form.
I've yet to perfect it--it's not the prettiest.
Would you like to see it?
Oh...
Shit!
Hmm, it still needs work.
Power alone is not enough.
To use it in a real fight,
I must be accurate as well.
Another question answered.
Still, I did feel decent impact.
She shouldn't be able to get far.
Stop hiding!
Our fight is not over yet!
You leave me no choice.
This might get a bit messy.
What are you doing?
Seriously? You want to see who's stronger?
Are you screwing with me?
You should know by now--
my raw strength is beyond yours!
Or are you now afraid of
putting your life on the line?
You've disappointed me.
Die.
You first.
Who the hell is that?
Where did you come from?
You lose.
Was a friend of yours hiding?
No, this is the same voice I heard before.
So who is this one?
Wonderful.
The tables have completely turned on me,
and I don't even know how.
So this is what it means
to put your life on the line.
You're stronger than I thought.
I doubt I can shake you off in time...
Is she controlling this thing?
You lose. Admit it.
I don't want to kill anyone!
Shuichi!
No, there are two of them!
This one must be a gatherer that transformed.
So who is she?
Can I ask you a question?
No!
If that girl is a normal human...
That gun was powerful enough to pierce my arm.
If she fires it...
Do you realize it?
I see.
All right then.
I lose.
Shuichi!
No, Clair!
I didn't think he'd transform back like that!
Don't worry about it.
It's his fault for doing something so dumb.
You're exactly right.
We put our lives on the line.
And I lost.
Kill me.
You really are dumb.
We gain nothing by killing you.
And yet we had to "put our lives
on the line" for your stupid fight.
How are you going to make this up to us?
Clair...
I'm sorry.
Give me your phone.
I don't have one.
You're lying!
It's true.
Why?
It's not manly!
Lady... Don't you think it's time
you put some clothes on?
I can't! I left them somewhere back there.
If you don't have a phone,
give me your address and phone number.
Ooh, nice!
Let me have it, too! And you two, give me yours.
Shuichi?!
I didn't notice!
He was downwind from us,
so I didn't catch his scent!
Don't try to run, now.
I got some lovely pictures of your faces.
Even if you run back to town, I'll find you.
Me and my friends are gonna
make you feel real special, girl.
You can't go making a ruckus
like that in these mountains...
Or some dangerous type like me
is going to find you.
From now on, you're my slaves.
I'm thankful...
You're clearly low-life scum...
Huh?
...so I'll have no second
thoughts about killing you.
He killed...
Ah, that's great.
You're so powerful--I thought
all the monsters were like you.
It looks like that's not the case!
So... What should I do?
You've got to help us look for coins, of course!
I'm sure you'll have plenty
of chances to test your strength.
I look forward to it.
You can wait till you heal, if you want.
You broke some ribs, didn't you?
Huh?
Uh... Are you okay?
You gave me this, didn't you?
Thank you.
What's your relationship with that girl?
I turn into the costume thing,
and she gets inside and fights.
Yeah... I didn't do anything this time, either.
Was splitting up her idea?
Huh?
No, it wasn't.
--That idiot said he'd be bait,
and I could run away.
--Idiot?!
--That idiot said he'd be bait,
and I could run away.
That's why I set it up that way.
I hated that plan though.
If I'm going to die, I want to die with Shuichi.
I see.
Shuichi, you're a real man.
All right. I'll join you.
You have my life.
Great! We should probably go back
before this guy's friends come.
I just found our next prey, too.
"Episode 6: Gatherers"